I don't know how to say this without being an a**hole, but if you think that there shouldn't be gun
regulation, I don't care. I'm not interested in having a conversation with you. I'm not interested
in having a discussion with you. I don't care. Like, I don't care about your opinion. You clearly
are not paying attention, so you're not somebody who responds to logic. So why would I think that
you're going to respond to me? I don't, y'all be in the comments leaving these f***ing dissertations,
you know, and all of this, I'm like, I don't care. I don't care what you think. You're watching people
get murdered every day and are still saying things like, we need to focus on mental health and have
absolutely no suggestions on what that even means. You don't even understand that in order to focus on
mental health, we would need to rebudget. We would need to actually allocate funds from things. Yes,
taxes if it needs to be raised. Like, you don't even understand that. You just throw out things
just so you can keep your little pow pow.